# **RESUME**

# Tejas Dilip Burumkar

At. Sujata Shopping Center Navgaon Road, "C" Wing, "B" Building, 2nd Floor, Room No. 212 Navgaon Road, Bhaynder (East)

Pin Code: 401105

# Email Id: tejas.burumkar@gmail.com Mob No.: 9049674227/ 8087770949

#### **Objectives**

• To pursue a professionally satisfying growth and challenging career. Seeking a quality environment where my knowledge can be shared and enriched for the organization's and self's growth.

## **Summary of Experience**

 Possessing two years of vast experience in the field of Computer Hardware & Networking where Planning, Implementation, Administration, and troubleshooting are involved with multiple platforms of OS viz., Microsoft Windows XP, 2003, 2008, and Windows 7, mac.

### **Expertise**

- Identifies, diagnoses, and resolves Level One problems for users of the mainframe, personal Computer software and hardware, Internet, and new computer technology.
- Provides one-on-one end-user problem resolution over the phone for user-approved Personal Computer (PC) software.
- Diagnoses and resolves end-user network or local printer problems, PC hardware problems, and mainframe, e-mail, Internet, WLAN, and local-area network access problems.
- Coordinates timely repair of PC equipment covered by third-party vendor maintenance agreements.
- Able to provide a full range of support and client relationship services ranging from first through to third-line support and customer on-site visits.
- Able to work independently and within a team-spirited environment.
- Attention to detail with a desire to create high-quality products.
- Strong presentation skills.
- Good knowledge and understanding of the network infrastructure and protocols such as TCP/IP, HTTP, etc.,
- Desktop (PCs, Laptops, and Peripherals) hands-on experience for both hardware and software
- Helps install local area network cabling systems and equipment such as network interface cards, and hubs. and switches.
- Groups customers by keywords for profiling, sales, and marketing campaigns, and training.
- Supports multi-message campaigns via e-mail, mail, etc.



#### **Work Experience**

#### Company:

- Chirag Cyber Cafe, Alibag 2016-2017
- Vinee Enterprises, Alibag 2017-2018
- Company pinnacle infotech, Mumbai 2019-2020
- Accma Computer Ltd, Mumbai 2021-2022
- Studio Next, Sony Entertainment 2022-2023
- Team lease service, Mumbai 2023-2024
- Designation: Desktop Support Engineer.
- Possessing one and a half years of vast experience in the field of computer Hardware and Networking where Planning, Implantation, Administration and Troubleshooting is involved with multiple platforms of OS viz., Microsoft Windows XP, 2003,2008, Windows 7.

#### Job Responsibilities

- Managing user accounts and giving share & security level permissions.
- Responsible for installing, setting up, maintaining the network, and configuring the
- peripherals, cabling, and types of equipment accordingly as per the requirement.
- Responsible for maintaining the company strategy like designing, implementing, and supporting enterprise network components.
- Responsible for monitoring whether all the components are available for successful communication.
- Responsible for maintaining the Backup network, hardware, software, and files regularly as per the company policies.
- Timely analysis of whether any repairs or replacements are
- needed. Managing the base of theserver & creating new user
- accounts.
- Responsible for troubleshooting Microsoft Windows issues.
- Responsible for configuring & troubleshooting Microsoft Outlook accounts.
- Responsible for creating new Microsoft Outlook accounts for new users.
- Monitoring complete network & providing network statistics.
- Responsible for the installation of the operating system Windows 7.
- Responsible for installing software like antivirus, MS-office, adobe & Acrobat Reader, etc.
- Responsible for maintaining the network & troubleshooting network-related issues. Responsible
- for maintaining & troubleshooting network printers.
- Responsible for troubleshooting Internet issues.
- Responsible for sharing the network printers.
- Knowledge of Outlook Configuration & Troubleshooting.
   Knowledge of active directory.

#### **Academic Qualification**

## Academic:

S.S.C from K.V.Patnus, Mangaon (Mumbai University) with 55.92% in 2007

One year Advance Certified Course in Computer Hardware & Networking Diploma Associate Certified from (NIITAPS).2015 to 2016

H.S.C from Industrial Jr. College, Alibag (Mumbai University) with 35.00% in 2016

BCA from YCMOU of Nasik with 82.66% in 2019

#### Technical Skills:

- Ticketing system management
- Good at Presentation & Communication skills.
- Customer service skills

#### **Assets**

- Hardworking, Self-confident, meets deadlines on tasks entrusted and hasample analyzing
- capacity. Takes the initiative and no additional directions are required once work is explained and assigned.

#### **Hobbies**

- Singing, Table tennis, and caroms. Reading, Football
- Books.
- Net Surfing.

#### **Personal Information**

Married status: Single.
Date of Birth: 09-01-1992

Languages Known: English, Hindi, and Marahi

Joining: Immediately.

#### Declaration

I now declare that the above information provided is true to the best of my knowledge and belief.

# - Tejas Burumkar